<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cheer For Peer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="google_maps_key" templateMergeStrategy="preserve" translatable="false">
        AIzaSyCbNPy5hqDEQFNNRXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX
    </string>

    <string name="step_of">Step %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="section_format">Section : %1$d</string>

    <string name="about_text">The best android implementation of material UI components. This app implemented based on Google Design Guidelines.
    </string>
    <string name="terms_conditions">
        Welcome to Cheers for Peers!

\n\nThese terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Cheers For Peers Website, located at cheersforpeers.com.

\n\nBy accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Cheers for Peers if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.

\n\nThe following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: Client, You and Your refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company\'s terms and conditions. \"The Company\", \"Ourselves\", \"We\", \"Our\" and \"Us\", refers to our Company.
\n\nCookies
\n\nWe employ the use of cookies. By accessing Cheers for Peers, you agreed to use cookies in agreement with the Cheers For Peers Privacy Policy.

\n\nMost interactive websites use cookies to let us retrieve the user\’s details for each visit. Cookies are used by our website to enable the functionality of certain areas to make it easier for people visiting our website. Some of our affiliate/advertising partners may also use cookies.

\n\nLicense
\n\nUnless otherwise stated, Cheers For Peers and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on Cheers for Peers. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may access this from Cheers for Peers for your own personal use subjected to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.

\n\nYou must not:

\n\nRepublish material from Cheers for Peers
\n\nSell, rent or sub-license material from Cheers for Peers
\n\nReproduce, duplicate or copy material from Cheers for Peers
\n\nRedistribute content from Cheers for Peers
\n\nThis Agreement shall begin on the date hereof. Our Terms and Conditions were created with the help of the Terms And Conditions Generator and the Privacy Policy Generator.

\n\nParts of this website offer an opportunity for users to post and exchange opinions and information in certain areas of the website. Cheers For Peers does not filter, edit, publish or review Comments prior to their presence on the website. Comments do not reflect the views and opinions of Cheers For Peers,its agents and/or affiliates. Comments reflect the views and opinions of the person who post their views and opinions. To the extent permitted by applicable laws, Cheers For Peers shall not be liable for the Comments or for any liability, damages or expenses caused and/or suffered as a result of any use of and/or posting of and/or appearance of the Comments on this website.

\n\nCheers For Peers reserves the right to monitor all Comments and to remove any Comments which can be considered inappropriate, offensive or causes breach of these Terms and Conditions.

\n\nYou warrant and represent that:

\n\nYou are entitled to post the Comments on our website and have all necessary licenses and consents to do so;
\n\nThe Comments do not invade any intellectual property right, including without limitation copyright, patent or trademark of any third party;
\n\nThe Comments do not contain any defamatory, libelous, offensive, indecent or otherwise unlawful material which is an invasion of privacy
\n\nThe Comments will not be used to solicit or promote business or custom or present commercial activities or unlawful activity.
\n\nYou hereby grant Cheers For Peers a non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, edit and authorize others to use, reproduce and edit any of your Comments in any and all forms, formats or media.

\n\nHyperlinking to our Content
\n\nThe following organizations may link to our Website without prior written approval:

\n\nGovernment agencies;
\n\nSearch engines;
\n\nNews organizations;
\n\nOnline directory distributors may link to our Website in the same manner as they hyperlink to the Websites of other listed businesses; and
\n\nSystem wide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls, and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.
\n\nThese organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Website information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products and/or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party\’s site.

\n\nWe may consider and approve other link requests from the following types of organizations:

\n\ncommonly-known consumer and/or business information sources;
\n\ndot.com community sites;
\n\nassociations or other groups representing charities;
\n\nonline directory distributors;
\n\ninternet portals;
\n\naccounting, law and consulting firms; and
\n\neducational institutions and trade associations.
\n\nWe will approve link requests from these organizations if we decide that: (a) the link would not make us look unfavorably to ourselves or to our accredited businesses; (b) the organization does not have any negative records with us; (c) the benefit to us from the visibility of the hyperlink compensates the absence of Cheers For Peers; and (d) the link is in the context of general resource information.

\n\nThese organizations may link to our home page so long as the link: (a) is not in any way deceptive; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party\’s site.

\n\nIf you are one of the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must inform us by sending an e-mail to Cheers For Peers. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Website, and a list of the URLs on our site to which you would like to link. Wait 2-3 weeks for a response.

\n\nApproved organizations may hyperlink to our Website as follows:

\n\nBy use of our corporate name; or
\n\nBy use of the uniform resource locator being linked to; or
\n\nBy use of any other description of our Website being linked to that makes sense within the context and format of content on the linking party\’s site.
\n\nNo use of Cheers For Peers logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark license agreement.

\n\niFrames
\n\nWithout prior approval and written permission, you may not create frames around our Webpages that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Website.

\n\nContent Liability
\n\nWe shall not be hold responsible for any content that appears on your Website. You agree to protect and defend us against all claims that is rising on your Website. No link(s) should appear on any Website that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.

\n\nYour Privacy
\n\nPlease read Privacy Policy

\n\nReservation of Rights
\n\nWe reserve the right to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Website. You approve to immediately remove all links to our Website upon request. We also reserve the right to amen these terms and conditions and it\’s linking policy at any time. By continuously linking to our Website, you agree to be bound to and follow these linking terms and conditions.

    </string>


</resources>